

Katlego Matshwi

CANDIDATE ATTORNEY

•

0614078939

×

MATSHWIKATLEGO@GMAIL. COM

_

2152 BLOCK GG,

Q

Soshanguve,

0152

2

https://www.linkedin.com/in/katlego-matshwi-260498158/

Skype

0

Website

ABOUT ME

Katlego Matshwi is an LLB student at the University of South Africa, having skills as a Programmer developing websites, mobile application and software, and on the other hand has previous work experience in which he dealt with Labour Law, Family Law (Divorce), Motor Vehicle Accidents and matters relating to Gender Based Violence, Katlego has been involved in debates and technology competitions, in which he was able to advance his skills in regards to his future legal profession

ACHIEVEMENT

- Winning 1st place in the Financial Sector Conduct Authority hackathon -https://www.instagram.com/p/CsRHBCts
 ooc/
- https://www.itweb.co.za/content/lwr

https://www.itweb.co.za/content/lwr Kxq3KaE1qmg1o

Winning 1st place in AB4IR hackathon

 Winning 1st place in the UNISA debate indaba

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF LAWS: University of South Africa

(UNISA) - PRESENT

Electives: Conveyancing, and Banking and Finance

SOSHANGUVE HIGH SCHOOL -

Completed with Bachelor's Pass – Class of 2015

- Chairperson of the Learners Christian Movement
- Top 3 highest performing learners in my class [1:3]

EXPERIENCE

Legal Advisor

Dikiletsong Citizens Advise Bureau | September 2021 – January 2023

I worked in the organization as a volunteer, we assisted people with any matter that they required assistance in and as law students under the auspices of the legal practitioners working for the organisation we provided, inter alia legal advise for clients in the legal matters.

- Handling of files, includes, taking client's instructions, opening and closing a file, editing a file and providing solutions to client
- Communicating all parties of interest
- Attending to the needs of a matter
- We dealt with, inter alia, Labour matters, family matters, estate execution matters, Divorce matters

Para-Legal

Ntozake Attorneys | March 2021 – July 2021

I was volunteering in the Law Firm, my function was that of a candidate attorney, I consulted with clients, communicate with other professionals and due to the fact that I didn't not have right of appearance I would in such instance sit and observe what another candidate attorney is doing and have notes in that regard and during my work I was Supervised by the senior attorney.

- Consulting and taking instruction from clients
- Communicating with parties of interest
- Attend to issuing, filing, serving at Court and attend to matters on Caseline Management System
- Conducting legal research
- Matters dealt with are, divorce, labour, gender based violence, execution of estate, unlawful arrest, Motor vehicle accident(Road Accident Fund)

Programmer / IT Support

Free-lancing | 2018 - present

I am a self- taught Programmer, and though I cannot be employed due to the fact that I do not have a formal certification to prove my education in this regard, I have free-lanced for companies and individuals dealing with the developments of websites, mobile applications and software, sometimes I develop the systems from scratch sometimes I add to what was already done

- Project Management and Supervision
- Programming Mobile application and websites
- Configuring personal computers, printers, routers and mobile phones

REFFERENCES

- Mr Kgothatso Rufus Motsogi, Senior Administrator (Fellow Student), Dikeletsong Citizens Advice Bureau.) | 081 845 2266
- Mrs Queen Nthite, Founder and CEO, Queen Nthite | 083 767 1188
- Ms Dimakatso Lubisi, Friend and Student I assist, University of Walter Sisulu | 063 603 1699
- Mr Brian Sbanyoni, Graphic Designer & friend | 072 229 5407